

# **DMITRII LIKHACHEV**

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### **CONTACT INFO**

**L** + 971-58-856-9932

☑ lihachevd87@gmail.com

• Dubai.UAE

**in** My LinkedIn

My GitHub

@lds196

My Portfolio

### **EDUCATION**

2021-2022

It-Incubator: React Frontend Developer RS School: JavaScript/Front-end #1 RS School: JavaScript/Front-end #0

#### 2005-2010

Urals State University of Railway Transport, faculty of railway construction, speciality - Engineer

#### 2007-2010

Urals State University of Railway Transport, faculty of Economics and Finance, speciality - Commerce specialist

### **LANGUAGES**

English, B1 (in progress)

Russian, native

### ABOUT ME

Hi! I'm frontend developer with experience about 1 year in creating SPA using React, Redux, TypeScript. Knowledge in user interface, testing, and debugging processes. I improving my skills in this direction and plan to expand them with newtechnologies, such as React Native. I usually spend my free time reading IT-literature, doing sports and improving my English. Open to your suggestions.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## 06.2022 - PRESENT My projects as frontend developer (part-time):

## Task-manager

• Stack: React, TypeScript, Redux (Toolkit), RestApi, Storybook Redux-thunk, Router-dom, Axios, Mui, Formik, Redux-Form,

## Social-Network

 Stack: React, TypeScript, Redux, RestApi, Router-dom, Axios, Ant design, Formik, Redux-Form, Jest

## Mama-Pizza

• Stack: React, TypeScript, Redux Toolkit, RestApi, Router-dom,

03.2022 - 06.22

## Second educational projects:

| Songbirds | Online-Zoo | Gem Pazzle |

Stack: JS / CSS / SASS/ HTML

01.2022 - 03.22

# First educational projects:

Travel | Momentum

• Stack: JS / CSS / SASS/ HTML

2010 - 2022

## **Head engineer Railway Transport**

Lead a construction teams service of railway, supervise the work of construction equipment preparation of reports on work planning and control of completed work, financial responsibility, development of technical documentation.

### **SKILLS**

- React/Redux (Toolkit)
- TypeScript/JavaScript
- Axios/Rest API
- Unit Test/Jest
- StoryBook
- React router dom, React Hooks
  Git
- MUI/Ant Design
- Formik/React Hook Form
- Styled Components
- Postman
- HTML/CSS/SCSS